hatch.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy Statement

Hatch Ltd. and Hatch Technologies Ltd. and their respective affiliates (collectively, “Hatch”) is committed to protecting your personal privacy. This statement outlines how we collect, use and protect the personal information that you provide to us. Hatch is bound by applicable privacy laws and all employees and officers of Hatch are expected to comply with this Privacy Statement. 

###  What personal information do we collect?

As this website provides the opportunity to apply for employment, the personal information that you provide to us in the application process will be stored and processed by a third party based in the United States and transferred to relevant Hatch employees for the purposes of considering you for career opportunities within Hatch. We may also collect information from public sources, educational institutions and other third parties such as former employers and referees to verify or add to information you have provided to us. 

#### Use and disclosure of information

Hatch is committed to neither use nor disclose personal information that it has collected, other than the purpose for which it was collected or any reasonable secondary purpose, including compliance with applicable laws. It is Hatch’s policy to obtain your written consent before it uses personal information for a purpose or in a manner different to the purpose or manner that was disclosed to you. However Hatch may collect and provide statistics about the web site and its users to other third parties. To assist us in providing a quality service to you and to evaluate our website a "cookie" (a data file that may be written to your computer by a web site) may be used. Only anonymous operating system data is collected such as domain, browser and IP address. No personal information can be viewed and no data can be accessed on your hard drive or other storage facilities.

####  Accessing and accuracy of your personal information

When you complete an application form via the Hatch website, you become registered as a user and you will be able to change and update your personal information you have provided at any time. As an applicant for employment and if you become an employee you have certain rights in relation to the personal information held by us.

####  Information storage and security

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information from disclosure other than as permitted by this Privacy Statement. We take all reasonable security measures to protect personal information from loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification or disclosure. As far as permissible under law, you acknowledge that Hatch accepts no responsibility for the unauthorized access of personal information held by Hatch. You can also play an important role in keeping your information secure by maintaining the confidentiality of any password and login details used on this site. 

####  Consent

Visiting this site will provide an anonymous record which can be used for statistical analysis to allow us to optimize the website performance. However you may provide data voluntarily which will be recorded and used for the purpose for which it has been provided. By the provision of this data you consent to its use as described in this privacy statement.

####  Links

This web site contains links to employment opportunities in most countries in which Hatch operates. Before disclosing your personal information on any other link within the Hatch website, we advise you to examine any specific privacy Terms and Conditions contained within those links.

####  Changes to this Statement

As we plan to keep our privacy statement current, this information can be subject to change. When appropriate, a revised Privacy Statement will be posted on the website which will incorporate any such changes. Please return periodically to review the latest policy. 

####  Country Specific Privacy Statements 

Detailed requirements for specific countries, which prevail over the Global Privacy Statement to the extent of any inconsistency, are linked below:

  * Privacy Statement - Australia

####  Privacy issues

If you have a complaint or require further information about how Hatch handles personal information or privacy issues, please contact us at [Privacy@hatch.com](mailto:Privacy@hatch.com)
